http://www.apposite-tech.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?When registering your product or contacting us you may be asked to enter your: name, company name, job title, e-mail address, mailing address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, product model, and product serial number.What do we use your information for?The email address you provide may be used to send you information, in addition to receiving occasional company news and updates. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit your personal information.Do we use cookies?We use Google Analytics remarketing codes to log when users view specific pages or take specific actions on a website. The tool uses “cookies,” which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google. This allows us to provide targeted advertising in the future. If you do not wish to receive this type of advertising from us in the future you can opt out using the opt-out page.We do not and will not allow any third party to use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Neither we nor Google will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any Personally Identifiable Information from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information.This website also uses a cookie to determine the first time, returning, and unique visits to the site. The website includes a Facebook Like button and social widgets which are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook Inc. that may use cookies and collect user data.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://www.apposite-tech.com/terms-of-use/.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on December 13, 2018.Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.Apposite Technologies LLC17835 Ventura Blvd. Ste 211Los Angeles, CA 91316United Statesinfo@apposite-tech.com
Products
Netropy
NetropyVE
Linktropy
Linktropy Mini
Menu
Netropy
NetropyVE
sales@apposite-tech.comsupport@apposite-tech.com+1 (310) 477-9955
Linkedin
Twitter
Copyright ©2020 Apposite Technologies. All Rights Reserved | Site Map | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
